[Music]
In
2002, when Dung had just graduated
from Teacher Training College, a
family acquaintance introduced her to Manual.
Since then, she's been involved with Manual. It was a really
big turning point, and
Dung considered the choice between
teaching and
customer service. Both involve a
lot of communication; you can interact with
people, and Dung likes
dynamic, communicative work.
Initially, Dung started
working in Vietnam at the Tien
Giang office, where her job was to
assist customers with their
questions or
requests. Later,
Dung moved to the customer service department, managing the
fee collectors and
supervising the customer service department. There were
many memorable experiences during the customer service process.
One memory that Dung remembers most is when
a customer with
leukemia went directly to the
hospital to help her.  The procedures and the
payment process... Honestly, when I
went to meet the customers, I was very
moved and felt that the work I was
doing was very worthwhile, and I
felt proud of my job.
From then on, I loved my job even
more and I believed even more in the
company's development direction, as well as having
faith that the company would always
grow and become strong. When I moved on to the
role of customer service supervisor at the
Tien Giang office, it wasn't long before
another opportunity came
my way. This new opportunity was related
to family happiness. While working in
customer service at the Tien Giang office, I
met my husband. Manol Life, perhaps, acted
like a matchmaker,
not only giving me a
good, stable job that
I love, but also having a
huge impact on my family.
Manol Life is truly a company where employees
feel they are
working in a very
professional and supportive environment.  This is an opportunity for
career development. At the same time,
I feel happy and
enjoy my work because I sense the
humanistic aspect in the work I have been
doing
[music].